

Francesco Giuseppe Leccese

Date of birth: 27/12/1986

Address: Via Generale Dalla Chiesa 24/a - Bari(ITA)

Mail: franekdev86@gmail.com

Phone number (ITA): +39 327 096 3560

Doctor in *Marketing and Business Communication* and *Front End Developer* with a six years career in an ICT company and two years of programming experience. I have completed my Bachelor's Degree in Marketing and Business Communication at "Università degli Studi di Bari" (Faculty of Economics and Commerce) and attended 1000+ hours coding bootcamp to learn new markup and programming languages while sharpening existing skills. I started my career in an ICT company as *first line IT consultant*, progressed it as *second line assistant* and *product support engineer* for reaching eventually the position of *IT Team Manager*. I am currently working as a freelance *front-end* developer and would like to apply my knowledge and passion for IT and coding to a talented engineering team. I have a passion for IT and web developing and professional growth.

Work Experience

01/2023 - ongoing

FRONT END DEVELOPER (freelance at FranekDev)



My portfolio webpage: https://franekdev-portfolio.netlify.app

My github profile: https://github.com/Franek-86

- Create, build, and maintain your websites and web applications.
- Focus on aesthetic factors like layout, user interface and other visual imagery in order to make your website more visually appealing and easy to use.
- Deep care of the overall style of your app combined with the focus on the actual functionality and usability of your application.
- It's possible to view my latest work on my "projects" page from my portfolio website, you can reach it by clicking here or by going to the following path https://franekdev-portfolio.netlify.app/projects.



FRONT END DEVELOPER at Developing.it (Bari - Italy)

- · Working in teams with a backend developer I have been fully in charge of creating the front-end interface of companies management systems built with Laravel.
- · Working in teams with other front end developers I collaborated in developing several Wordpress websites, all of them built with custom PHP templates.
- Fully in charge of the creation of a client website, from start to finish, built with a custom Worpress PHP template and working with the most advanced Wordpress functionality.
- Fully in charge of the creation of a client website created from start to finish with Wordpress Elementor.
- Fully in charge with the front end creation of the company internal "smart office" full responsive web application. This is an application used for opening gate, main door, set boiler temperatures and others. I created the front-end side of this web application using React.

08/2022 - 12/2022



IT CUSTOMER SERVICE TEAM MANAGER at Fujitsu (Łódź - Poland)

- · Coordinate the service desk team members in their daily duties of attending to clients who come to make inquiries and facilitate good customer service culture in team members
- Evaluate and assess service delivery performance metrics and carry out survey on clients to weigh the level of service delivery in the company
- · Keep record of daily operations at the desk for tracking of customer needs, services rendered and future reference
- · Create a mode of operations to be adhered to by team members in order to maintain good routine and orderliness
- Delegate specific service desk responsibilities to team members to create specialization and increase service delivery pace
- Review all client complaints, rectify issues and liaise with appropriate departments to handle complex issues in a bid to provide more effective solutions
- · Observe service desk operation techniques to determine how effective they are and implement new techniques when old ones are ineffective

09/2019 - 07/2021



IT CUSTOMER SERVICE EXPERT TECHNICIAN at Fujitsu (Łódź - Poland)

- · Analyze and resolve customer concerns and problems, diagnose the root cause, and document interactions.
- · Provide on-call and ongoing troubleshooting, technical, and hardware advice and suggestions.
- Support remote and local upgrades, installations, and maintenance.



IT CUSTOMER SERVICES AGENT at Fujitsu (Łódź - Poland)

- Providing IT support to users located worldwide
- · Handling of company's high severity impact incidents
- · Constant and enthusiastic participation to internal trainings (Excel, Networking, Assertive communication, ITIL, Time Managing)

12/2016 - 06/2017

SENIOR ACCOUNTING ASSOCIATE in AP departamnet at **DXC Technology** (Łódź - Poland)



- · Accounts Payable in JDE
- · Invoice processing, handling invoices from the arrival to post.

01/2016 - 11/2016



JUNIOR ACCOUNTING ASSOCIATE in AR department at CONDUENT (Łódź - Poland)

- Account Receivable in SAP
- DD/DC proposals
- MEC reporting according to strict directivess

09/2015 - 11/2015

CUSTOMER SERVICE ADVISOR SouthWestern Business Process Services Poland Sp. z o.o

02/01/2012 - 20/05/2014



ASSISTANT PRODUCER MEC Produzioni (Bari - Italy)

- · Assistant producer of a prime time television programme "Striscia La Notizia".
- Handling production of televised reports aired by Mediaset S.p.a on the Italian national channel "Canale 5". (2 years)

Education

- · Responsive Web Design (freeCodeCamp.org certification) (<u>*</u>)
- · JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures (freeCodeCamp.org certification) (<u>*</u>)
- HTML&CSS Tutorial and Projects Course 2023 (Flexbox&Grid)(Udemy certification)
- · Javascript Tutorial and Projects Course (2023)(Udemy certification) 🔥

- React 18 Tutorial and Projects Course (2023) (Udemy certification)
- Node Tutorial and Projects Course (2023) (Udemy)

Certificate of Attendance accredited by The British Council

Marketing and Communication Bachelor's Degree at "Università degli Studi di Bari"



- IC3 Internet and Computing Core Certification
- "Development of film product" education course at A. S. FORCINEMA (Rome Italy)
- High School Diploma in Science at "Liceo scientifico Enrico Fermi" (Bari Italy)



Computer Skills & Languages

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- **BOOTSTRAP**
- **WORDPRESS**
- **JAVASCRIPT**
- PHP
- **JQUERY**
- **VANILLA.JS**
- **REACT.JS**
- **VUE.JS**
- **NODE.JS**
- **MONGODB**
- MySQL
- **GIT**
- MS Office programs (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Outlook)
- Italian language (native)
- English language (fluent)
- Polish (basic)